Guide to the Ralph Rydholm papers, 1936-2014 and undated RL.11279
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Audiovisual Materials, 1962-2009 and undated; 4
  - Untitled, Undated (Box AV4, Film-reel RL11279-F16-033)
  - Untitled, Undated (Box AV4, Film-reel RL11279-F16-034)
  - Untitled, Undated (Box AV4, Film-reel RL11279-F16-035)
  - Untitled, Undated (Box AV4, Film-reel RL11279-F16-036)
  - Untitled, Undated (Box AV4, Film-reel RL11279-F16-037)
  - Untitled, Undated (Box AV5, Film-reel RL11279-F16-038)
  - Untitled. VOG-1-30, Undated (Box AV5, Film-reel RL11279-F16-039)
  - Untitled. TP-113-30, Undated (Box AV5, Film-reel RL11279-F16-040)
  - Untitled. 60 Quick Rev., Undated (Box AV5, Film-reel RL11279-F16-041)
  - Untitled. Quick Revised 30, Undated (Box AV5, Film-reel RL11279-F16-042)
  - Untitled. VO5-301-30, Undated (Box AV5, Film-reel RL11279-F16-043)
  - Untitled. TP-113-30, Undated (Box AV5, Film-reel RL11279-F16-044)
  - Adorn "Lifestyle" #1. GSTA0403. 16mm production print, Undated (Box AV5, Film-reel RL11279-F16-045)
  - Adorn "Local Meeting" GSTA0523, Undated (Box AV5, Film-reel RL11279-F16-046)
  - Adorn "Mrs. B" :30, Undated (Box AV5, Film-reel RL11279-F16-047)
  - Alberto Culver BP-1-4RC-30 "Blonde", Undated (Box AV5, Film-reel RL11279-F16-048)
  - Alberto Culver Calm Spray Powder "10 Times" PD-75-30 30 sec. prod. 5308, Undated (Box AV5, Film-reel RL11279-F16-049)
  - Alberto Culver Mighty White 2 "Janet and Jerry" TP-114-30, Undated (Box AV5, Film-reel RL11279-F16-050)
  - Alberto Culver "Man's Day" AVVO-1083 answer print, Undated (Box AV5, Film-reel RL11279-F16-051)
  - Alberto Culver "Traveling Girl" AVAP-1053, Undated (Box AV5, Film-reel RL11279-F16-052)
  - Alberto Culver Alberto Culver "Traveling Girl" Sets" AVCM-1013 contract, Undated (Box AV5, Film-reel RL11279-F16-053)
  - Alberto Culver VO5 Deodorant "10 Times" AP1-2-30. 30 sec. prod. 5309, Undated (Box AV5, Film-reel RL11279-F16-054)
  - Alberto Culver VO5 Hairdressing "Brushing" VO5-324-30 answer print, Undated (Box AV5, Film-reel RL11279-F16-055)
  - Alberto Culver VO5 Hairdressing "The Weatherbeater" VO5-331C-30 JWT answer print, Undated (Box AV5, Film-reel RL11279-F16-056)
  - Alberto Culver VO5 Hairspray with Miral "Scissors Slice" HS-349-30 30 sec. prod. 5267 answer print, Undated (Box AV5, Film-reel RL11279-F16-057)
  - Alberto Culver VO5 Hairspray "Steam Bath" HS-352-30. 30 sec. prod. 5314 answer print, Undated (Box AV5, Film-reel RL11279-F16-058)
  - Alberto Culver "Women's Lib" AVCO-0083, Undated (Box AV5, Film-reel RL11279-F16-059)
  - Blondes American Style "Here Comes the Blondes" #8 :30 J.W. Thompson, Undated (Box AV5, Film-reel RL11279-F16-060)
  - Enden "For People Who Don't Have Dandruff", Undated (Box AV5, Film-reel RL11279-F16-061)
  - Enden EN-EXP-23 "MMM", Undated (Box AV5, Film-reel RL11279-F16-062)
  - Enden "Stay in the Shower" EN-EXP-16, Undated (Box AV5, Film-reel RL11279-F16-063)
  - Gillette "15 Year Old" GSRP3043 with logo, Undated (Box AV5, Film-reel RL11279-F16-064)
  - Gillette "Boxing" Rev. 16mm release print. GSRP2203, Undated (Box AV5, Film-reel RL11279-F16-065)
  - Gillette "Father and Son" 45" GSRP2154. Rev. release print, Undated (Box AV5, Film-reel RL11279-F16-066)
  - Gillette "Father and Son" 45" GSRP2154. Rev. release print. Barb Minisee, Undated (Box AV5, Film-reel RL11279-F16-067)
  - Gillette West Logo GSRP-3113, Undated (Box AV5, Film-reel RL11279-F16-068)
  - ITT Thorp "Family" ITWI1232, Undated (Box AV5, Film-reel RL11279-F16-069)
  - Ken-L-Ration "Baa" KB-30-211, Undated (Box AV5, Film-reel RL11279-F16-070)
  - Ken L Ration "Family Dog" KP-60-224, Undated (Box AV5, Film-reel RL11279-F16-071)
  - Ken L Ration Mighty Morsels "Newspaper" KM-60-410, Undated (Box AV5, Film-reel RL11279-F16-072)
  - Ken L Ration Burger "Border" KB-30-235, Undated (Box AV5, Film-reel RL11279-F16-073)
  - Ken L Ration Burger "Doghouse" reduction, 1968 (Box AV5, Film-reel RL11279-F16-074)
  - Ken L Ration Burger "Hotel" KB-33-30-247, 1968 (Box AV5, Film-reel RL11279-F16-075)
  - J. Walter Thompson "Life of Horseless Carriage" FPDV4053 :30, Undated (Box AV5, Film-reel RL11279-F16-076)
  - J. Walter Thompson "Horseless Carriage" FPDV4056 :60, Undated (Box AV5, Film-reel RL11279-F16-077)
  - Sears Merry Month of May Sale #2092. 60 sec. color reduction, Undated (Box AV5, Film-reel RL11279-F16-078)
  - Sears Compactor "Thanksgiving" N2-1071-6530 30 sec. clr. 5400 kelvin, Undated (Box AV5, Film-reel RL11279-F16-079)
  - Sears Dishwasher "Chef Louis" N6-1071-6530 JWT#2116. 30 sec. clr. 5400 kelvin, Undated (Box AV5, Film-reel RL11279-F16-080)
  - Taystee "Slices" 60-312 60 sec., Undated (Box AV5, Film-reel RL11279-F16-081)
  - Toni "Beach JWT. GSTN 0303. :30, Undated (Box AV5, Film-reel RL11279-F16-082)
  - Toni "Beach JWT. GSTN 0303. :30, Undated (Box AV5, Film-reel RL11279-F16-083)
  - Toni "Beach JWT. GSTN 0323. :30, Undated (Box AV5, Film-reel RL11279-F16-084)
  - Mentholatum "Arizona Sun" :30, Undated (Box AV5, Film-reel RL11279-F16-085)
  - Mentholatum "Little One" MVOT-2307 :30, Undated (Box AV5, Film-reel RL11279-F16-086)
  - Mentholatum "Medicine Chest Skin" MVOT-5303 answer print, 1976 (Box AV5, Film-reel RL11279-F16-087)
  - Mentholatum "Mother and Son" MVRU-4305. Contractual from edit/chgo. 9/11/75, 1975 (Box AV5, Film-reel RL11279-F16-088)
  - Mentholatum "Philadelphia Story" MDHL-5301. Lotion/rev. :30, Undated (Box AV5, Film-reel RL11279-F16-089)
  - Mentholatum "The Box" MVRU-2301. 30 sec. color JWT, Undated (Box AV5, Film-reel RL11279-F16-090)
  - Platinum Plus "Jerry West D.E. Man" GSRP-3153 30 sec. color JWT, Undated (Box AV5, Film-reel RL11279-F16-091)
  - Platinum Plus "Father and Son" GSRP-2093 30 sec. color. JWT, Undated (Box AV5, Film-reel RL11279-F16-092)
  - Uncle Ben's Rice "Dining Room" MRMP-1366. TV print quick revised, Undated (Box AV5, Film-reel RL11279-F16-093)
  - Uncle Ben's Rice "Dining Room" MRMP-1296 alternate :60, Undated (Box AV5, Film-reel RL11279-F16-094)
  - Uncle Ben's Rice "Kitchen" MRMP-1346 :60 tv print quick revised, Undated (Box AV5, Film-reel RL11279-F16-095)
  - Uncle Ben's Rice "Ed McMahon's Kitchen" MRCR-0016 :60, Undated (Box AV5, Film-reel RL11279-F16-096)
  - Uncle Ben's Rice "Mrs. Johnson" MRMP-0086, Undated (Box AV5, Film-reel RL11279-F16-097)
  - Uncle Ben's Rice Presentor 30-5287-R4 30 sec. color, Undated (Box AV5, Film-reel RL11279-F16-098)
  - Uncle Ben's Rice Presentor 60-5286-R4 60 sec. color, Undated (Box AV5, Film-reel RL11279-F16-099)
  - Uncle Ben's Rice "Quick" #993 :60, Undated (Box AV5, Film-reel RL11279-F16-100)
  - Vic Tandy Health Club "Side By Side" :60, Undated (Box AV5, Film-reel RL11279-F16-101)
  - 2nd Quarter International excluding UK, 1989 (Box AV6, Video-cassette RL11279-VHS-001)
  - 2nd Quarter UK, 1989 (Box AV6, Video-cassette RL11279-VHS-002)
  - 3rd Quarter International excluding UK, 1989 (Box AV6, Video-cassette RL11279-VHS-003)
  - 3rd Quarter UK, 1989 (Box AV6, Video-cassette RL11279-VHS-004)
  - 4th Quarter UK, 1989 (Box AV6, Video-cassette RL11279-VHS-005)
  - IAC/JWT advertising targeted at children, Undated (Box AV6, Video-cassette RL11279-VHS-006)
  - Advertising-related film clips for speeches, Undated (Box AV6, Video-cassette RL11279-VHS-007)
  - AICP judges reel, 1995 (Box AV6, Video-cassette RL11279-VHS-008)
  - American Association of Advertising Agencies: Conversations on Agencies (Burt Manning with John Pepper and Herb Kelleher), Undated (Box AV6, Video-cassette RL11279-VHS-009)
  - AMP 89, 1989 (Box AV6, Video-cassette RL11279-VHS-010)
  - Best of British, Undated (Box AV6, Video-cassette RL11279-VHS-011)
  - Beyond the Beltway with Bruce DuMont. Guests: Ralph Rydholm, Lee Newcom, Doug Dobmeyer, 1996 (Box AV6, Video-cassette RL11279-VHS-012)
  - British TV Awards 1987-1988 (Box AV6, Video-cassette RL11279-VHS-013)
  - British Television Advertising Awards, 1989 (Box AV6, Video-cassette RL11279-VHS-014)
  - British Television Advertising Awards, 1991 (Box AV6, Video-cassette RL11279-VHS-015)
  - British Television Advertising Awards, 1991 (Box AV6, Video-cassette RL11279-VHS-016)
  - British Television Advertising Awards, Undated (Box AV6, Video-cassette RL11279-VHS-017)
  - CAF Creative Panel Lunch. Ralph Rydholm, moderator., 1993 (Box AV6, Video-cassette RL11279-VHS-018)
  - Cannes, 1987 (Box AV6, Video-cassette RL11279-VHS-019)
  - Cannes, 1988 (Box AV6, Video-cassette RL11279-VHS-020)
  - Cannes part 1, 1991 (Box AV6, Video-cassette RL11279-VHS-021)
  - Cannes entries Eurocom part 1, 1991 (Box AV6, Video-cassette RL11279-VHS-022)
  - Cannes part 2, 1991 (Box AV6, Video-cassette RL11279-VHS-023)
  - Cannes parts 1 and 2, 1991 (Box AV6, Video-cassette RL11279-VHS-024)
  - Cannes part 2, 1995 (Box AV6, Video-cassette RL11279-VHS-025)
  - Cannes part 1, 1995 (Box AV6, Video-cassette RL11279-VHS-026)
  - Cannes, Undated (Box AV6, Video-cassette RL11279-VHS-027)
  - Century 21 pitch, Undated (Box AV6, Video-cassette RL11279-VHS-028)
  - Euro RSCG Cannes entries, Undated (Box AV6, Video-cassette RL11279-VHS-029)
  - Dole Productions "Whatever It Takes" promotional video, Undated (Box AV6, Video-cassette RL11279-VHS-030)
  - Euro RSCG Tatham. Hoover spots, 1996 (Box AV7, Video-cassette RL11279-VHS-031)
    Steam Vac Jr.; Twist & Vac; Steam Vac Deluxe; Steam Vac Deluxe/Agitator kid open; Wet/Dry Vac Supreme. SFO406 rough cut and track dub. 5:00
  - Euro RSCG Tatham. IL&M, Undated (Box AV7, Video-cassette RL11279-VHS-032)
  - Euro RSCG Tatham. Off the Street Club 1999. (Box AV7, Video-cassette RL11279-VHS-033)
  - Euro RSCG Tatham. Pacific Data Images., Undated (Box AV7, Video-cassette RL11279-VHS-034)
  - Euro RSCG Tatham. Ralph Rydholm My Lunch with George Lazarus. CAF Tribute Dinner., Undated (Box AV7, Video-cassette RL11279-VHS-035)
  - Euro RSCG Tatham. Ralph Rydholm speech, VCMA annual meeting, 1997 (Box AV7, Video-cassette RL11279-VHS-036)
  - European food reel, Undated (Box AV7, Video-cassette RL11279-VHS-037)
  - Food spots dub, Undated (Box AV7, Video-cassette RL11279-VHS-038)
  - GGT reel, Undated (Box AV7, Video-cassette RL11279-VHS-039)
  - Harvard AMP, Undated (Box AV7, Video-cassette RL11279-VHS-040)
  - Harvard reunion AMP, 1989 (Box AV7, Video-cassette RL11279-VHS-041)
  - Euro RSCG Tatham. World View, Undated (Box AV7, Video-cassette RL11279-VHS-042)
  - Hill & Knowlton. PXL 2000 the Revolution in Video Technology for Kids. 8:00 (Includes Julia), Undated (Box AV7, Video-cassette RL11279-VHS-043)
  - J. Walter Thompson. AAA spots., 1995 (Box AV7, Video-cassette RL11279-VHS-044)
    Characters rev. ZJWA-5009; Lines rev. ZJWA-5008; Scenes rev. ZJWA-5010. 1:30
  - J. Walter Thompson. Ralph's JWT reel, Undated (Box AV7, Video-cassette RL11279-VHS-045)
  - J. Walter Thompson. Conclave, 1984 (Box AV7, Video-cassette RL11279-VHS-046)
  - J. Walter Thompson. Conclave, 1984 (Box AV7, Video-cassette RL11279-VHS-047)
  - J. Walter Thompson. Conclave, 1984 (Box AV7, Video-cassette RL11279-VHS-048)
  - J. Walter Thompson. Conclave, 1984 (Box AV7, Video-cassette RL11279-VHS-049)
  - J. Walter Thompson. Ed Maroney's 30th anniversary video, 1994 (Box AV7, Video-cassette RL11279-VHS-050)
  - J. Walter Thompson. Limits rough cut, Undated (Box AV7, Video-cassette RL11279-VHS-051)
  - J. Walter Thompson. Miller/Lowenbrau rough cut, 1985 (Box AV7, Video-cassette RL11279-VHS-052)
  - J. Walter Thompson. Pepsi spots, 1985 (Box AV7, Video-cassette RL11279-VHS-053)
    12 o'clock; 6 o'clock; 8 o'clock; 10 o'clock. Director and Chicago cuts. Editors Choice, Inc. 6:00
  - J. Walter Thompson. Ralph Rydholm television seminar, Undated (Box AV7, Video-cassette RL11279-VHS-054)
  - J. Walter Thompson. Ralph's reel JWT Chicago, Undated (Box AV7, Video-cassette RL11279-VHS-055)
  - J. Walter Thompson. USA video storyboard winners, 1982 (Box AV7, Video-cassette RL11279-VHS-056)
  - J. Walter Thompson. Worst of international, regional, U.S. ads, Undated (Box AV7, Video-cassette RL11279-VHS-057)
  - Lindsay & Stone Advertising television demo., 1989 (Box AV7, Video-cassette RL11279-VHS-058)
    Point Beer "Party's Over"; UWHC "Heart Care"; Chancery "Shame on You"; Valley Bank "Frustrated"; :Point Beer "Just Be Yourself"; APT "Play in the Woods"; Chancery "A Little Sax"; UWHC "Pediatrics"; Valley Bank "Airplane"; Point Beer "Don't Forget"; UWHC "Feel at Home"; Valley Bank "Clown"; Chancery "Pig".
  - M*A*S*H USO party at Hyatt Regency Maui. 28:00, 1982 (Box AV7, Video-cassette RL11279-VHS-059)
  - Moses Anshell agency demo reel, Undated (Box AV7, Video-cassette RL11279-VHS-060)
  - Nabisco grocery reel, Undated (Box AV8, Video-cassette RL11279-VHS-061)
  - NARC, Undated (Box AV8, Video-cassette RL11279-VHS-062)
  - Needham Harper. Joel Hochberg on Callaway Show (shows Pepsi spots), 1985 (Box AV8, Video-cassette RL11279-VHS-063)
  - Ogilvy & Mather. Advertising Women of New York Lifetime Achievement Honoring Charlotte Beers, 1997 (Box AV8, Video-cassette RL11279-VHS-064)
  - Partnership for a Drug-Free America. Toward a Drug-Free America, 1988 (Box AV8, Video-cassette RL11279-VHS-065)
  - Pepsi spots, 1985 (Box AV8, Video-cassette RL11279-VHS-066)
    12, 6, 8, 10 O'clock spots. EC85-104 JWT. Editors Choice, Inc. 6:00
  - Quarterly Review of UK Advertising, Undated (Box AV8, Video-cassette RL11279-VHS-067)
  - Ralph's Harvard reunion, 1991 (Box AV8, Video-cassette RL11279-VHS-068)
  - RSCG 15 best commercials, 1989 (Box AV8, Video-cassette RL11279-VHS-069)
  - Rydholm brand personality reel, Undated (Box AV8, Video-cassette RL11279-VHS-070)
  - S.A., S.P., U.K., Canada, Undated (Box AV8, Video-cassette RL11279-VHS-071)
  - Spanish commercials, Undated (Box AV8, Video-cassette RL11279-VHS-072)
  - Tatham Euro RSCG. Around the World Holiday Toast, 1992 (Box AV8, Video-cassette RL11279-VHS-073)
  - Tatham Euro RSCG. Around the World Holiday Toast, 1992 (Box AV8, Video-cassette RL11279-VHS-074)
  - Tatham Euro RSCG. Cannes, 1993 (Box AV8, Video-cassette RL11279-VHS-075)
  - Tatham Euro RSCG. Cannes, 1996 (Box AV8, Video-cassette RL11279-VHS-076)
  - Tatham Euro RSCG. Euro RSCG reel, Undated (Box AV8, Video-cassette RL11279-VHS-077)
  - Tatham Euro RSCG. Hardee's Kids' Meal, 1996 (Box AV8, Video-cassette RL11279-VHS-078)
  - Tatham Euro RSCG. Hoover, 1997 (Box AV8, Video-cassette RL11279-VHS-079)
    Fetch; 3 Guys; Plexi 2; Brush Shot; Oh No. Avid rough cut and track
  - Tatham Euro RSCG. Hoover, 1997 (Box AV8, Video-cassette RL11279-VHS-080)
    Harness the Wind; Adams/Stevens; Fetch. Avid rough cut and track. 2:45
  - Tatham Euro RSCG. Hoover infomercial, 1996 (Box AV8, Video-cassette RL11279-VHS-081)
  - Tatham Euro RSCG. Hoover "Life of Brian G" 18:00, 1998 (Box AV8, Video-cassette RL11279-VHS-082)
  - Tatham Euro RSCG. Our First 50 Years 1946-1996 (Box AV8, Video-cassette RL11279-VHS-083)
  - Tatham Euro RSCG. P&G brand equity tape, Undated (Box AV8, Video-cassette RL11279-VHS-084)
  - Tatham Euro RSCG. Procter & Gamble Metamucil spots, 1996 (Box AV8, Video-cassette RL11279-VHS-085)
    Gaffer; Guide. Several versions. Avid rough cut and track
  - Tatham Euro RSCG. United Industries Corporation current creative UI and top competitors, 1995 (Box AV8, Video-cassette RL11279-VHS-086)
    Cutter, Off, Hot Shot, Raid, Spectracide, Ortho, Roundup, Peters, Miracle Gro, Scotts brands represented. 5:00
  - Tatham Laird & Kudner. Illinois Bell spots, 1991 (Box AV8, Video-cassette RL11279-VHS-087)
    Adult; Teen. V-2557.
  - Tatham Laird & Kudner. Illinois Bell spots, 1990 (Box AV8, Video-cassette RL11279-VHS-088)
    Montage; Lincoln Park; Not a Good Day; It's Me. ST90-2483. 18:00
  - Tatham RSCG. Tatham Revival Hour with Rev. Ralph and the Tatham Singers, 1992 (Box AV9, Video-cassette RL11279-VHS-089)
  - Tim Croneweth demo reel, Undated (Box AV9, Video-cassette RL11279-VHS-090)
  - Tatham RSCG. Hoover, 1992 (Box AV9, Video-cassette RL11279-VHS-091)
    Iain Calder; Piggyback. Video dub. 19:04
  - Euro RSCG Tatham. Cannes Lions 1997: Grand Prix, Journalists Award, all Gold, Silver and Bronze Lions. Tape 2 (Box AV9, Video-cassette RL11279-VHS-092)
  - Euro RSCG Tatham. Cannes Lions 1997: Grand Prix, Journalists Award, all Gold, Silver and Bronze Lions. Tape 1 (Box AV9, Video-cassette RL11279-VHS-093)
  - Tatham Euro RSCG. Hoover 8 spots tied, 1997 (Box AV9, Video-cassette RL11279-VHS-094)
  - Euro RSCG Tatham. Hoover spots, 1999 (Box AV9, Video-cassette RL11279-VHS-095)
    Sleepover/Wind Tunnel Canister new. MYHV-5813, MYHV-5822. :45
  - This Time Around, Pepsi, Undated (Box AV9, Video-cassette RL11279-VHS-096)
  - This Time Around, Pepsi, Undated (Box AV9, Video-cassette RL11279-VHS-097)
  - Television Advertising in Japan (Robin Restall). 29 spots., approximately 1982 (Box AV9, Video-cassette RL11279-VHS-098)
    Brands include Seiko Hybrid, Bigman, Daihatsu, National Panasonic, Suntory, Big John, Nissan, Valcam, Pepsi, Domestos, Honda, Etiquette Toothpaste, Albert Maxime Grassian, Tory's Puppy Dog, Vassarette, Walcoal, Parco Water, Onward Jane Moore. Celebrities include Paul Newman, Marcello Mastroani, Sammy Davis Jr.
  - Tape from Will's office, Undated (Box AV9, Video-cassette RL11279-VHS-099)
  - Wells Rich Green BDDP. United Industries spots, 1995 (Box AV9, Video-cassette RL11279-VHS-100)
    Hot Shot and Spectracide spots. Bug Security; Refrigerator; Stop Sign; Weed Warrior
  - WLS-TV Chicago Advertising (Rydholm featured), 1988 (Box AV9, Video-cassette RL11279-VHS-101)
  - American Bakeries Company. Dan Sorkin speaking for Taystee Bread. Sound Studios Inc. 10", 1962 (Box AV10, Audio-phonodisc RL11279-PD-001)
  - Armour. My Fair Ladies, record #6. Webb Recording Co. 10", 1962 (Box AV10, Audio-phonodisc RL11279-PD-002)
  - BC (Buzz Cason) and the Dartz, An American Saturday Night. Track Records 1001, NR16086. 12", 1986 (Box AV10, Audio-phonodisc RL11279-PD-003)
  - Florence Warner, Another Hot Night. Mercury SRM-1-4019. 12", 1980 (Box AV10, Audio-phonodisc RL11279-PD-004)
  - J. Walter Thompson Manila. A Christmas Wish, Various Artists, etc. B/w Pasko, Pasko Na, Coy Sanchez. M. Villapando, comp. 7", 1985 (Box AV10, Audio-phonodisc RL11279-PD-005)
  - J. Walter Thompson/Oscar Mayer, Celebrating 20 Years of Harmony. 12", 1980 (Box AV10, Audio-phonodisc RL11279-PD-006)
    Side A: The Meatpacker Suite, Arr. Joe Godfrey. Side B: Der Fliegende Hollander Overture (The Flying Dutchman, Richard Wagner). University of Wisconsin Symphony Orchestra, Catherine Comet, conductor.
  - Sandy Lankford, Sandy's Country. Total Eclipse TES-1000. 12", 1974 (Box AV10, Audio-phonodisc RL11279-PD-007)
  - Young & Rubicam/Allied Van Lines. When You Move, Move with Allied radio spots. Universal U-17193. 12", 1963 (Box AV10, Audio-phonodisc RL11279-PD-008)
  - Young & Rubicam/American Bakeries. Taystee Bread regular version. T-2002. 12", 1962 (Box AV10, Audio-phonodisc RL11279-PD-009)
    Tracks: 1. JAP; 2. Blumley Castle; 3. Straight Shooter; 4. Super Market; 5. Soap Opera.
  - Alan O'Day. Somewhere She Is Sleeping, mono and stereo. Viva VIV-7679. 7", 1973 (Box AV11, Audio-phonodisc RL11279-PD-010)
  - Buzz Cason. Places, mono and stereo. Janus Records J258. 7", 1976 (Box AV11, Audio-phonodisc RL11279-PD-011)
  - Buzz Cason. Race Drivin' Man b/w Come Back. Caprice CA-1974. 7" (Box AV11, Audio-phonodisc RL11279-PD-012)
  - Ed Bruce. It's Not What She's Done (It's What You Didn't Do) b/w Mamas Don't Let Your Babies Grow Up to Be Cowboys. United Artists UA-XW732-Y. 7", 1975 (Box AV11, Audio-phonodisc RL11279-PD-013)
  - Ed Bruce.July You're a Woman, mono and stereo. United Artists UA-XW353-W. 7", 1973 (Box AV11, Audio-phonodisc RL11279-PD-014)
  - Eric Weissberg. Dueling Banjos b/w End of a Dream. Warner Bros. WB-7659. 7", 1972 (Box AV11, Audio-phonodisc RL11279-PD-015)
  - Florence Warner. Anyway I Love You, mono and stereo. Epic 8-50152. 7", 1975 (Box AV11, Audio-phonodisc RL11279-PD-016)
  - Styx. Lady b/w Children of the Land. Wooden Nickel WB-10102. 7", 1973 (Box AV11, Audio-phonodisc RL11279-PD-017)
  - Sugarloaf/Jerry Corbetta. Don't Call Us, We'll Call You b/w Texas Two-Lane. Claridge 402. 7", 1974 (Box AV11, Audio-phonodisc RL11279-PD-018)
  - Victy Silva. All Summer Long b/w I Got You. Bronze BRO-43. 7", 1977 (Box AV11, Audio-phonodisc RL11279-PD-019)
  - Some of the Best of Music Makers Vol. IV. MM-1206. 7", Undated (Box AV11, Audio-phonodisc RL11279-PD-020)
    Side I: General Motors, Squirming Irma radio; Galey and Lord tv; Stella D'Oro tv; Thom McAn, Liverpool T's radio; Fanta soft drink radio; Silk 'n Satin tv; Olin Mathieson, pool tv. Side 2: Polaroid Swinger radio and tv; Alka Seltzer, Laboratory tv; Noblesse cigarettes radio and tv; L&M cigarettes, Folk radio and tv; Ballet Stockings tv; Braniff; Wing tv; Chevrolet, Dots and Dashes tv.
  - Actors Gym Powerpoint, Undated (Box AV11, Video-disc RL11279-OP-001)
  - American Bar Association. National Symposium on the American Jury System., 2006 (Box AV11, Video-disc RL11279-OP-002)
  - American Bar Association. ABA Commission on the American Jury Poster and Bookmarks, 2006 (Box AV11, Video-disc RL11279-OP-003)
  - El Valor. Imagine the Possibilities., 2006 (Box AV11, Video-disc RL11279-OP-004)
  - Executive Service Corps (ESC of Chicago) 30th Anniversary Video, 2008 (Box AV11, Video-disc RL11279-OP-005)
  - F.M. Neil, Undated (Box AV11, Video-disc RL11279-OP-006)
  - F.M. Neil, 2004 (Box AV11, Video-disc RL11279-OP-007)
  - Gossage: The Disc of Gossage, Undated (Box AV11, Video-disc RL11279-OP-008)
    Howard Gossage. Contents: Gossage gallery; correspondence; Earth Day; Family Album; Gossage at college; Guest speaker Gossage; Marget Larsen; Sweat shirt; Powerpoint; Additional resources.
  - JWT Chicago: RIP JWT commercials, 2009 (Box AV11, Video-disc RL11279-OP-009)
    Contents: The reel; the Uncola story
  - JWT Chicago: RIP JWT videos, 2009 (Box AV11, Video-disc RL11279-OP-010)
    Contents: 100 years; Hancock welcome; Old Blue Eyes; The warriors; Beat us.
  - JWT Chicago: Reunion party photo album, 2009 (Box AV11, Video-disc RL11279-OP-011)
    Contents: Party posters; reunion pictures; Jeff York caricatures; historical snaps
  - McNally: American Express commercial, Undated (Box AV11, Video-disc RL11279-OP-012)
  - MATA video tag, Undated (Box AV11, Video-disc RL11279-OP-013)
  - Mis Padres Mis Maestros/My Parents My Teachers (El Valor), Undated (Box AV11, Video-disc RL11279-OP-014)
  - Neil's PDF's, Undated (Box AV11, Video-disc RL11279-OP-015)
  - Radio-Mercury Awards: Radio's Best Advertising of 1995, 1996 (Box AV11, Video-disc RL11279-OP-016)
  - RSCG: Bon Anniversaire. Orchestre Symphonique d'Europe, 1989 (Box AV11, Video-disc RL11279-OP-017)
  - RSCG Invitation (20th anniversary), 1989 (Box AV11, Video-disc RL11279-OP-018)
  - The Year's Best Campaigns: '98 Effie Winners interactive yearbook, 1999 (Box AV11, Video-disc RL11279-OP-019)